Finding aid for Smith Club of Western Connecticut records CA.MS.00330
Smith College Archives
Smith Club of Western Connecticut records
1947-2004
Smith College Archives
Smith Club of Western Connecticut
CA.MS.00330
0.833 linear feet (2 containers)
These records contain minutes, photographs, membership directories, publicity materials, clippings, and president's notebooks documenting the activities of the Smith Club of Western Connecticut.
Biographical / Historical
The Smith Club of Western Connecticut was active beginning in 1947 when it was called the Waterbury Smith Club. The club was refounded in 1953 as the Waterbury-Litchfield Hills Smith Club. It wasn't until 1964 that the designation 'Western Connecticut' began to be used. Throughout its history the club undertook many fundraising efforts and social events, and was active in promoting Smith to prospective students in the area.
Scope and Contents
This collection including notebooks, membership records and directories, agendas and minutes, photographs, press releases, scrapbooks, and annual reports all relating to the events, fundraisers, and basic functions of the club.
Conditions Governing Access
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Smith Club of Western Connecticut Records were donated over a period of time to the Smith College Archives from a variety of sources.
Smith College - Alumni and alumnae - History - Sources
- Alumnae Association - General, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Alumnae Council, 1984-91 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports, 1977-92 (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
- Annual Reports - Committees, 1982-96 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Annual Reports - Treasurer, 1981-83; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Board Member Job Descriptions, 1977; 1985-88 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Book Awards - Correspondence, 1991-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Book Awards - General, 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bylaws, 1969-95 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Clippings, 1975-2003; undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1979-81; 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Directories, 1972-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
- Events, 1981-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Inauguration, Jill Ker Conway, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Internship Information, 1997; undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Mailings - Announcements and Invitations, 1982-99; undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Meeting, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Membership, 1991-92; undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Minutes and Agendas, 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
- Newsletters, 1978-2004; undated (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
- Notebook, B. Schancupp, President, 1993-2004 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
- Obituaries, 1994-2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Photographs, 1994-97 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Photographs - Earthwatch, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Presidents and Boardmembers, 1947-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Press Releases and Public Relations, 1978-81; undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Scrapbook, 1970-77 (Box 2, Folder 16)